techimo.com 2011-05-27

# TechIMO.com - The enthusiast community where your opinion counts.

**All Enthusiast, Inc.'s Privacy Policy**

All Enthusiast, Inc.'s TechIMO.com respects the privacy and security of its users. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect information during your visits to understand what differentiates you from each of our millions of other users.

In order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this statement disclosing the privacy practices for the entire TechIMO.com site. Additional terms and conditions regarding the collection and use of your information are also be provided to you before you register for our site. Here, you will learn what personally identifiable information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**What information is collected:**

TechIMO.com collects certain information from and about its users in three ways -- directly from the user, from our Web server logs, and with cookies.

User-Supplied Information: When you register for TechIMO.com, we may ask you for your name, email address, and some other personal information. The more accurate information you volunteer, the better we are able to customize your TechIMO.com experience.

Server Log Information: When you visit an Internet Web site, you disclose certain information about yourself, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the time of your visit, and the referring location (e.g., the Site or page that offered a link to a TechIMO.com page). All Enthusiast, Inc.'s TechIMO.com, like many other sites, records this basic information about visits to its site.

Cookies: In order to offer and provide a customized, personal service, TechIMO.com uses cookies to store and help track your information as you travel throughout the site. For example, we may use cookies to help remind us who you are and to deliver content and services based upon your account information. In addition, third party advertising networks may issue cookies when serving advertisements.

Cookies are simply pieces of information that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. The use of cookies is relatively standard and you will likely find them used on most other major Web sites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that certain areas of many sites may not function properly if you set your browser to not accept cookies or if you reject a cookie.

You should remember that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, such as in message boards, through e-mail, discussion groups, or in chat areas, your information can be collected and used by others. Allthough All Enthusiast, Inc. tries to protect your personal information, All Enthusiast, Inc. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. You are also solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords you set up and/or any account information.

**How and When Information is Used** :

We use information in different ways, depending on the type of information: User-supplied information: This information is used for purposes such as personalization and verification.

Web Server Logs: This information helps us identify which areas of our site are of interest to our visitors. TechIMO.com also collects the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of its visitors for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.

Cookies: We use cookies to let you use our services more easily and to let us keep track of certain statistical information that helps us improve our site. Cookies allow us to save passwords and preferences for you so that you won't have to re-enter them the next time you visit.

**How We Protect Your Information:**

The privacy and protection of your personal information is vitally important to us. TechIMO.com does not make personal information available to any third parties without your permission. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners regarding your TechIMO.com usage are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user.

Your access to some services and content is password protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. TechIMO.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. You should not disclose your user name and password to others. In addition, if applicable, you should remember to sign out of your TechIMO.com account or service at the end of each session. You may also wish to close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, despite our efforts to protect your personal information, TechIMO.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or to or from our online products or services. You transmit all such information to us at your own risk. However, once we receive your trandmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

**Who Has Access to the Information:**

Except as described below, All Enthusiast, Inc.'s TechIMO.com will not willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about its users to any third party without first receiving that user's permission. All Enthusiast, Inc.'s TechIMO.com may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to protect the rights or property of All Enthusiast, Inc.'s TechIMO.com. All Enthusiast, Inc.'s TechIMO.com will use its best efforts to contact you if All Enthusiast, Inc. is issued a subpoena or other legal process that requests your identity.

When you are at the TechIMO.com site and asked for personal information, you share that information with TechIMO.com alone, unless the service is offered in conjunction with another party. For example, some TechIMO.com services, such as our online store, are offered in conjunction with another company. In order to provide such co-branded services to you, it is necessary for us to share your personal information with the company offering the co-branded service. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of data by not using that particular service. If you choose to share your data with a provider of a co-branded service, you should understand that those providers may have separate privacy and data collection practices. All Enthusiast, Inc. has no control over and accepts no liability for these independent practices. Each provider shouldmore information regarding its privacy and/or use policies.

**Third Party Advertising:**

We use DoubleClick, Google, and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site, other sites and other interactive media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

**How to Correct Inaccuracies**

If you use another All Enthusiast, Inc. service, we may send you a confirmation e-mail confirming your new account and/or service. The message will be sent to the address that you supplied us and will describe ways for you to change or delete the account information provided. Remember to keep the confirmation e-mail as it will also contain information that will help you in case you run into problems accessing our services.

We welcome any questions or comments you have about TechIMO.com: please direct them to [our contact form](http://www.techimo.com/timo_contact.pl).
